{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Metal Stair Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40426/":{"taskOID":40426,"originalTaskOID":40426,"setID":718,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4608,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please enter the type of stairs (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6136,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Straight","answerDisplayText":"Straight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Curved","answerDisplayText":"Curved","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2503,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flared","answerDisplayText":"Flared","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1395,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Circular","answerDisplayText":"Circular","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5950,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Spiral","answerDisplayText":"Spiral","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3447,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Landing mid-stair","answerDisplayText":"Landing mid-stair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1447,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closed riser","answerDisplayText":"Closed riser","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4417,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Open risers (no risers)","answerDisplayText":"Open risers (no risers)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4617,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6610,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unstable staircase","answerDisplayText":"Unstable staircase","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5010,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Railing pulling out of wall","answerDisplayText":"Railing pulling out of wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4178,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New railing needed","answerDisplayText":"New railing needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":936,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Baluster(s) needed","answerDisplayText":"Baluster(s) needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4183,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"New tread(s) needed","answerDisplayText":"New tread(s) needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5050,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Re-weld","answerDisplayText":"Re-weld","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5048,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Re-paint","answerDisplayText":"Re-paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4610,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please enter the type of material (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5042,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Raw steel","answerDisplayText":"Raw steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7137,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wrought iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2709,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Galvanized steel","answerDisplayText":"Galvanized steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1098,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brass","answerDisplayText":"Brass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1141,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bronze","answerDisplayText":"Bronze","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4552,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Painted","answerDisplayText":"Painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4838,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Powder coated","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7108,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Wooden handrail","answerDisplayText":"Wooden handrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7095,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Wood treads","answerDisplayText":"Wood treads","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4608,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Stairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please enter the type of stairs (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6136,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Straight","answerDisplayText":"Straight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Curved","answerDisplayText":"Curved","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2503,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flared","answerDisplayText":"Flared","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1395,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Circular","answerDisplayText":"Circular","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5950,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Spiral","answerDisplayText":"Spiral","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3447,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Landing mid-stair","answerDisplayText":"Landing mid-stair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1447,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closed riser","answerDisplayText":"Closed riser","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4417,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Open risers (no risers)","answerDisplayText":"Open risers (no risers)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6136,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Straight","answerDisplayText":"Straight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1741,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Curved","answerDisplayText":"Curved","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2503,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flared","answerDisplayText":"Flared","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1395,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Circular","answerDisplayText":"Circular","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5950,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Spiral","answerDisplayText":"Spiral","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3447,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Landing mid-stair","answerDisplayText":"Landing mid-stair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1447,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closed riser","answerDisplayText":"Closed riser","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4417,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Open risers (no risers)","answerDisplayText":"Open risers (no risers)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4617,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6610,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unstable staircase","answerDisplayText":"Unstable staircase","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5010,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Railing pulling out of wall","answerDisplayText":"Railing pulling out of wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4178,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New railing needed","answerDisplayText":"New railing needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":936,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Baluster(s) needed","answerDisplayText":"Baluster(s) needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4183,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"New tread(s) needed","answerDisplayText":"New tread(s) needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5050,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Re-weld","answerDisplayText":"Re-weld","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5048,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Re-paint","answerDisplayText":"Re-paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6610,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Unstable staircase","answerDisplayText":"Unstable staircase","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5010,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Railing pulling out of wall","answerDisplayText":"Railing pulling out of wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4178,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"New railing needed","answerDisplayText":"New railing needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":936,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Baluster(s) needed","answerDisplayText":"Baluster(s) needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4183,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"New tread(s) needed","answerDisplayText":"New tread(s) needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5050,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Re-weld","answerDisplayText":"Re-weld","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5048,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Re-paint","answerDisplayText":"Re-paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4610,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please enter the type of material (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5042,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Raw steel","answerDisplayText":"Raw steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7137,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wrought iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2709,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Galvanized steel","answerDisplayText":"Galvanized steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1098,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brass","answerDisplayText":"Brass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1141,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bronze","answerDisplayText":"Bronze","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4552,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Painted","answerDisplayText":"Painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4838,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Powder coated","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7108,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Wooden handrail","answerDisplayText":"Wooden handrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7095,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Wood treads","answerDisplayText":"Wood treads","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5042,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Raw steel","answerDisplayText":"Raw steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7137,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wrought iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2709,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Galvanized steel","answerDisplayText":"Galvanized steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1098,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Brass","answerDisplayText":"Brass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1141,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bronze","answerDisplayText":"Bronze","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4552,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Painted","answerDisplayText":"Painted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4838,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Powder coated","answerDisplayText":"Powder coated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7108,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Wooden handrail","answerDisplayText":"Wooden handrail","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7095,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Wood treads","answerDisplayText":"Wood treads","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40426/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40426,"taskName":"Metal Stairs and Railings - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Metal Stairs and Railings","xmTaskDescriptor":"Metal Stair Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":285,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Metal iron wrought staircases staircase","textMessagingName":"Repr Metal Stair","rolloverLongDesc":"pre-fab units (typically used for side \u0026 rear entrances) can often be installed by a builder or carpenter, but any adjustments or customization would probably be handled by a specialist. Includes both interior \u0026 exterior staircases. Includes spiral staircases \u0026 fire escapes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes custom built \u0026 pre-fab stairs \u0026 fire escapes.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Metal Stairs and Railings.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Metal Stair Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Metal Stairs \u0026 Railings","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":51,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Metal Stairs \u0026 Railings Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Stairs and Railings - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Stairs \u0026 Railing Project","urlName":"Metal-Stairs-and-Railings-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal Stair Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Metal Railing Repair","searchKeywords":"Metal,iron,wrought,staircases,staircase,spiral,working,structure,build,Railings,balusters,building,stairway,Stairs","emcCategoryOid":-12049,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":718,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}